cybo.com 2019-05-08

# Cybo - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

· Cybo helps people find businesses. Cybo users can review the businesses.

· Using Cybo you permit the collection and use of personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

· Cybo collects user submitted account information to send notifications related to Cybo.

· Some of the information collected is not explicitly submitted by the user; we record your browser type, IP address, URL requested, referring URL and time. This information helps us diagnose server problems and improve our service.

· We reserve the right to transfer your personal information in the event of the transfer of ownership of Cybo, such as an acquisition or merger with another company.

· Like most Web sites, Cybo requires cookies to function properly. We use industry standard measures to protect your information.

· Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to this website. This enables it and its partners to serve ads based on your visits to this site and/or other sites on the internet.

· You may opt out of Google's cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/)

· Alternatively, you may opt out of third party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](https://www.aboutads.info/)

· We use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of this site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics to improve this site.

· We use Google Analytics "Advertiser Features" including Demographics and Interests reporting.

· [How Google uses data when you use partners' sites or apps](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).

· Google provides a way to opt out: [prevent your data from being used](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) by Google Analytics.

· We use various Google services or API's (e.g. Google Maps API). Here is a reference to the [Google Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).

· The Site is intended for general audiences and is not directed to children under 13 years old. If you post content for public view on the Site, we may distribute such Public Content to a wider audience by sharing it with third parties.

· We are a US website designed and intended for US audiences.

· If you have any questions please contact us.

Cybo Company  
P.O. Box 51121  
Eugene, OR 97405  
United States 

* * *

Thank you for your interest in Cybo.

Follow us to stay updated with new changes on the site.
